Fred Rochlin papers, 1694-2002 (bulk 1880-1930),
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 5: Photograph Files, 1850-1986, 19.75 linear ft.
  - Subseries: Exhibit Photographs, 1868-1929
    - La Francesa May Hermanos #1, Nogales, Sonora, Mexico. 1896 (Box 38)
    - La Francesa May Hermanos #2, Nogales, Sonora, Mexico. 1896 (Box 38)
    - Don Pedro Faerber, Magdalena, Sonora, Mexico. (Box 38)
    - Alexander Levin and his son, Henry. 1880 (Box 38)
    - Zeckendorf and Staab, On the Left, Tucson, Arizona Territory. 1878 (Box 38)
    - William and Julia (Frank) Zeckendorf and family. 1880 (Box 38)
    - Julia (Frank) Zeckendorf (Mrs. William). 1870 (Box 38)
    - Max Levy, Chicago Clothing Co., Port Townsend, WA. (Box 39)
    - Anna Frudenthal Solomon and her daughter Blanche Solomon Weinberger, Solomonville, AZ. 1900 (Box 39)
    - Ladies Hebrew Benevolent Society (Sorosis Sisterhood), Tucson, AZ. 1892 (Box 39)
    - Gabriel Levy #1, Signal, AZ. 1890 (Box 39)
    - Gabriel Levy #2, Signal, AZ. 1890 (Box 39)
    - Herman Walisch Store, Charleston, AZ. 1879 (Box 39)
    - Mayer, Lieberman & Co., Lordsburg, NM. 1882 (Box 39)
    - Rothschild & Co., Port Townsend, WA. 1870 (Box 39)
    - Gabriel Levy #3, Signal, AZ. 1890 (Box 39)
    - Waterman and Katz, Port Townsend, WA. (Box 39)
    - Kentucky Store, Port Townsend, WA. 1868 (Box 39)
    - Leopold Ephraim Office, Nogales, AZ. 1890 (Box 39)
    - Major Lugwig Ilfeld, Las Vegas, NM. 1916 (Box 40)
    - Josephine Sarah Marcus Earp (Mrs. Wyatt). (Box 40)
    - Leopold Ephraim and the Nogales Water Co., Nogales, AZ. 1901 (Box 40)
    - Grumpricht Ephraim. 1885-1890 (Box 40)
    - William Rosenberg #1, Tubac, AZ. 1915 (Box 40)
    - William Rosenberg 32, Tubac, AZ. 1910 (Box 40)
    - B. Cohen's Monte Carlo, Nogales, AZ. 1898 (Box 40)
    - Jacob Isaacson and Jennie Pierce Isaacson, Las Vegas, NM. 1880-1910 (Box 40)
    - Isaac Isaacson, Nogales, AZ. 1890 (Box 40)
    - A& B Schuster General Merchandise, St. John's, AZ. 1880 (Box 40)
    - Street Scene #1, No Location. (Box 40)
    - Street Scene #2, No Location. (Box 40)
  - Subseries: Oversize Photographs, 1868-1945
    - Johnson, Charles G.- Views of the Arizona and the Colorado River. 1868 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Portrait of Nathan Leeker. 1918 (Box 41)
    - Mexican Revolutionary Leaders. 1900-1920 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Military, Arials. 1940-1945 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Unknown Negatives. (Box 41)
  - Subseries: Panoramas, 1916
    - Featuring the New Military Base of the United States Army at the Mexican Border. 1916 (Box 42)
    - California Battery, USA, Troops on the Mexican Border, Nogales, Arizona. 1916 (Box 42)
    - United States Army Troops on the Mexican Border 1. 1916 (Box 42)
    - First Battalion First California Field Artillery, Nogales, Arizona. 1916 (Box 42)
    - United States Army Troops on the Mexican Border 2. 1916 (Box 42)
    - Fifth California from Mexico. 1916 (Box 42)
    - Early United States Army Camp, El Paso, Texas. 1916 (Box 42)
- Series 6: Oral Histories, 1.25 linear ft.
  Oral Histories contains interviews of Jewish individuals and families.
  - Appel (Victor) Goldbaum. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Copeland. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Cunig/ Elster. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Kirsch. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Nogales. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Unlabeled. (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Series 7: Postcards, 1900-1985, 3.75
  Postcards contains two subseries. Subseries 1: Michael Rochlin Postcard Collection (1900-1985) includes images of various locations throughout the Southwest, principally Nogales Arizona and Mexico. Subseries 2: General Postcards and Postmarks (1900-1930) includes images from around the United States.
  - Subseries: Michael Rochlin Postcard Collection, 1900-1985
    - Postcard Samples. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Notes and Partial Inventory. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Nogales. (Box 44)
    - Nogales, Mexico, Arizona. (Box 45)
    - Arizona, California, Nevada, New Mexico, Texas, Judaica, Unknown. (Box 46)
  - Subseries: General Postcards and Postmarks, 1900-1930
    - Postmarks (Box 47)
- Series 8: Ephemera, 1840-2001, 7.25 linear ft.
  Ephemera contains twelve subseries. Includes publications, pamphlets, maps, and ledgers divided by region. Subseries: Arizona (1880-1941), Subseries: California (1873-1981), Subseries: General (undated.), Subseries: Mexico (1891-1910), Subseries: Military (1940-2001), Subseries: Montana (1880-1900), Subseries: Nevada (undated.), Subseries: New Mexico (1840-1937), Subseries: New York (1840-1900), Subseries: South Dakota (undated.), Subseries: Texas (1858-1865), Subseries: Ledgers (1866-1899).
  - Subseries: Arizona, 1880-1941
    - Advertising Decal. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Brands and Marks. 1908 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Flagstaff. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Report. 1898 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Masons Lodge Proceedings. 1905 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Nogales. 1887-1928 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Nogales High School Yearbook. 1941 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Nogales, John T. Brickwood Court Case. 1912-1917 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Phoenix. 1920-1930 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Prescott. 1907 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Santa Cruz County. 1941 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Tucson. 1880-1900 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Tucson, The University of Arizona. 1900-1910 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Yuma. 1880-1900 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Subseries: California, 1873-1981
    - General. 1928-1938 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Judaica. 1968-1981 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles. 1925-1969 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Wells Fargo. 1873 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Subseries: General
    - Judaica. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Maps. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Unknown. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Subseries: Mexico, 1891-1910
    - Mexico. 1890-1910 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Subseries: Military, 1940-2001
    - 456th Bomb Group Souvenir Calendar. 1945 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - AAF Navigation School. 1940-1945 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Aircraft Navigation Manual. 1941 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Drawings. 1940-1945 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Fifteenth Air Force Association. 1990-1999 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Publications, 456th Bomb Group, Cerignola, Italy. 1990-1994 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Publications, 456th Bomb Group, Stornara, Italy. 1995-2001 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Crosshairs. 1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Military. 1998 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Polaris. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Schiffer Catalog. 1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Silk Maps, Italy. 1940-1945 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Subseries: Montana, 1880-1900
    - Montana. 1880-1900 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Subseries: Nevada
    - Nevada. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: New Mexico, 1840-1937
    - Albuquerque. 1937 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Cattle Brands. 1915 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Las Vegas. 1899 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Publications. 1840-1880 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Silver City. 1873 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Subseries: New York, 1840-1900
    - New York. 1840-1900 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Subseries: South Dakota
    - South Dakota. (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Subseries: Texas, 1858-1865
    - Texas, De Cordova, Jacob. 1858-1865 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Subseries: Ledgers, 1866-1899
    - Original and Duplicate, Leopold Ephraim Correspondence. 1894-1899 (Box 51)
    - Accounts Ledger. 1866-1867 (Box 52)